(hammer tapping)
(people chattering)
(upbeat music)
♪ Josie's on a vacation far away ♪
♪ Come around and talk it over ♪
♪ So many things that I wanna say ♪
♪ You know I like my
girls a little bit older ♪
♪ I just wanna use your love tonight ♪
♪ I don't wanna lose your love tonight ♪
♪ I ain't got many
friends left to talk to ♪
♪ Nowhere to run when I'm in trouble ♪
♪ You know I'd do anything for you ♪
♪ Stay the night but keep it undercover ♪
♪ I just wanna use your love tonight ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ I don't wanna lose your love tonight ♪
(upbeat music)
♪ Try to stop my hands from shaking ♪
♪ But something in my
mind's not making sense ♪
♪ It's been a while
since we were all alone ♪
♪ I can't hide the way I'm feeling ♪
♪ As you're leaving, please
would you close the door ♪
♪ And don't forget what I told you ♪
♪ Just 'cause you're right
that don't mean I'm wrong ♪
♪ Another shoulder to cry upon ♪
♪ I just wanna use your love tonight ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I don't wanna lose your love tonight ♪
♪ Yeah, I just wanna
use your love tonight ♪
♪ I don't wanna lose your love tonight ♪
♪ I just wanna use your love tonight ♪
♪ Lose your love ♪
♪ I don't wanna lose your love tonight ♪
♪ I don't wanna, I don't wanna ♪
♪ Your love ♪
♪ Lose your love tonight ♪
♪ I don't wanna lose your love tonight ♪
♪ Don't wanna lose your love tonight ♪